modthesims.info 2019-12-29

# Mod The Sims - Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

You can use this website anonymously. If you are logged out, we will not gather any identifying information about you. If you register an account and log in to it, we will collect your email address and registration IP address.

Your email address will only be used to contact you regarding your account, e.g. to send password reset emails, or to reply to emails you send via the "Send Private message as Email" pages. We will never pass your email address on to anyone else, unless we are legally required to do so.

If you want to change or delete the email address attached to your account, you can do so using the Edit Profile, or by emailing [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

If we ever have a data breach, we will notify affected users by email and by on-site notification within 7 business days of our discovery of the breach.

If we change this Privacy Policy, we will place a notification on all pages with a link to the updated policy, at least 14 days before the changes come into effect.

### Cookies

Mod The Sims uses cookies to keep you logged in. If you disable cookies, you will have to log in every time you visit the site.

In conjunction with our in-house advertising, we use third-party advertising companies to place customized advertisements on the pages you view on Mod The Sims. Our third-party advertising companies also separately place or recognize a cookie file on your browser in the course of delivering advertisements to Mod The Sims. These companies may use non-personal information collected by the cookies about your visits to the Site and other web sites in order to provide you with advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

Google Analytics may also place cookies on your computers, to anonymously analyse our website traffic. You can opt out of these cookies by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

### Contacting Us

If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, you can contact us at:  
[[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

This policy is effective from 9th November 2018.
